Contact

Mogro, Cantabria 655579880 (Home) mail@davidtor.es

www.linkedin.com/in/davidtor (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

Programación orientada a objetos Solución de problemas

Languages

Inglés (Professional Working)

Certifications

Professional Scrum Master I (PSM I)

David Tortajada Alonso

Freelance Java & Intershop Developer

Santander, Cantabria, Spain

Summary

Full Stack Engineer with several years of experience in Java development, including analysis, design, development, and deployment of enterprise applications.

Extensive knowledge in J2EE, JavaScript, and frameworks such as Spring. Also, knowledge in other languages and tools as Intershop, Oracle, Git, Linux, Dev-ops, AWS, Jira...

Looking for new challenges and opportunities to develop and acquire new skills on a professional level as well as on a personal level.

Experience

Profesional independiente
Freelance Java & Intershop Developer
November 2020 - Present (3 years 3 months)
Santander, Autonomía de Cantabria, España

Valtech

Freelance Intershop Developer January 2022 - August 2023 (1 year 8 months) Netherlands

Wunderman Thompson Commerce via SimplyCommerce Freelance Intershop Developer November 2020 - December 2021 (1 year 2 months) Netherlands

Nationale Postcode Loterij Intershop developer at Nationale Postcode Lottery via Incentro October 2017 - October 2020 (3 years 1 month)

Santander Area, Spain

Incentro

Intershop developer, Consultant July 2013 - October 2020 (7 years 4 months)

Santander Area, Spain

Intershop 7.x and full stack Developer for COOP, Wolters Kluwer and Novamedia .

Working remotely from Spain. Intershop versions 7.5, 7.6 and 7.7 Including a recent migration to 7.9.

We deal everyday with imports, user management, products, catalogues, promotions, content, images, replications, Solr, devops, linux and so on. 24/7 maintenance keeping all servers running smoothly. ISH Jira Scrum Git Oracle IS JDK8 ...

Developer for GStar RAW www.g-star.com

- · web aplication with Java, html5, css3, nodejs, angular
- · Scala, Play! framework
- · GIT
- · Eclipse, Netbeans
- · Scrum
- · Jenkins, Nexus CI
- · CMS tridion

Some projects with CMS Hippo and nodejs

- · Atag www.atag.nl
- · Air miles www.airmiles.nl
- · Wolters Kluwer www.wolterskluwer.com/
- · Rechtwijzer www.rechtwijzer.nl/

Coop Supermarkten Intershop developer at Coop via Incentro August 2017 - December 2019 (2 years 5 months) spain

Wolters Kluwer Intershop developer at Wolters Kluwer via Incentro March 2016 - August 2017 (1 year 6 months) Spain

G-Star RAW

Java developer at G-Star via Incentro July 2013 - March 2016 (2 years 9 months) Spain

Ayuntamiento de Santander. New Technologies Department Programador

January 2013 - July 2013 (7 months)

Aplicación interna para el servicio municipal de grúas.

- · Aplicacion y servicios web en una arquitectura de ncapas orientada a domínio.
- · VS2010, C#, .NET, entity framework, ext.net, WCF, Oracle

Quality Objects

Analista Programador

August 2008 - May 2012 (3 years 10 months)

Analista programador para el cliente Mutua Madrileña. www.mutua.es

- · Analista programador en el cliente Mutua Madrileña www.mutua.es
- · Desarrollando aplicaciones web con J2EE, RAD(Eclipse), Websphere y DB2
- · Soporte y mantenimiento de la web de Mutua Madrileña
- · Desarrollando y manteniendo diversas aplicaciones internas
- · Frameworks Spring, Hibernate, Struts y jQuery
- · Desarrollo de servicios web.

Indra

Programador

February 2007 - August 2008 (1 year 7 months)

Desarrollo de Plataforma Aseguradora para cliente Aviva (Vida y Pensiones):

- · Programación Web sobre patrón MVC en J2EE
- · Diseño UML sobre arquitectura MDA (AndroMDA)
- . Java, Javascript, JSP, UML, CSS, Ajax, Struts, Spring, Hibernate, SOA.

Education

Universidad de Zaragoza

Ingeniero Técnico en Informática de Sistemas, Ingeniería informática · (2000 - 2005)